<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>net.worldofpadman.WoP</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary=https://github.com/PadWorld-Entertainment/worldofpadman/blob/main/COPYING.md</project_license>
  <provides>
    <id>worldofpadman.desktop</id>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">net.worldofpadman.WoP.desktop</launchable>
  <name>World of PADMAN</name>
  <summary>Incredibly carefully designed and colorful freeware fun shooter for young and young-at-heart people</summary>
  <description>
    <p>**This is a community package of World of PADMAN and not officially supported by PadWorld Entertainment.**</p>
    <p>
      From the earliest PadMaps for Q3A came the mod PadWorld, followed by the next colorful evolution, World of PADMAN. Developed and headed by 
      cartoonist and illustrator ENTE, PadWorld Entertainment presents a freeware fun shooter, that's powered by an extended id-Tech3 graphics engine.
    </p>
    <p>
      WoP is the domain of ENTE's comic strip super-hero PADMAN and his motley crew. It's their mission to make your game with some seriously addictive fun, 
      whatever your skill level and whatever character role you jump into.
    </p>
    <p>
      Over the years maps have been revamped, bots improved, Killerducks kept hungry, weapons re-polished and much more! In all, there are 24 maps. Each 
      supports up to 7 game types, comprising WoP's unique Spray Your Color, Last Pad Standing, Big Balloon, and of course Capture The Lolly. Meet scaled-up 
      and richly detailed environments of everyday places, where imaginative characters go berserk with an array of colorful plastic weaponry and powerups. 
      Start rockin' to the soundtrack of Dieselkopf, and Neurological and listen to the Pad-Anthem, performed by Green Sun. So, grab your earphones!
    </p>
    <p>
      Not enough human players on public servers? Practice with bots and join the community on the official PadWorld server for the Padday community events, 
      every first Sunday of a month 7:00pm (CET).
    </p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://worldofpadman.net</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/PadWorld-Entertainment/worldofpadman/issues</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://github.com/PadWorld-Entertainment/worldofpadman</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default"><image>https://a.fsdn.com/con/app/proj/worldofpadman/screenshots/309709.jpg</image></screenshot>
    <screenshot><image>https://a.fsdn.com/con/app/proj/worldofpadman/screenshots/309711.jpg</image></screenshot>
    <screenshot><image>https://a.fsdn.com/con/app/proj/worldofpadman/screenshots/309713.jpg</image></screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <developer_name>PadWorld Entertainment</developer_name>
  <releases>
    <release version="1.6.2" date="2021-11-28"/>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">intense</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
</component>
